## Farel Reyhananda Nugraha

### Software Developer (Full Stack)

<u>farel.reyhananda@gmail.com</u> | <u>www.linkedin.com/in/farel-reyhananda</u>

Jakarta, Indonesia

A passionate software engineer with 3+ years of experience in web software development. Stem from the same passion to grow, I have managed to learn a handful of skills, such as web development, machine learning, OHS, CAD, as well as geophysics skills that I receive from college study

## **Work Experiences**

#### **Fullstack Engineer**

Aug 2023 - Nov 2024

JULO | Jakarta, Indonesia

- Collection and repayment related backend improvements (API, code improvement, Optimizing API performance)
- Scheduling task for payment reminder, FDC, populate data
- API integration with third party-related backend work (Callback)
- Frontend website (CRM internal site, external site, webview)
- Frontend related communication templates (email, sms, push notification)

#### **Backend Engineer**

Aug 2021 - May 2023

Finku | Jakarta, Indonesia

- Developed API for various features using NestJS + mongodb (Gamification, Homepage, Loan, Internal uses, third-party API integration)
- Web scraping with Puppeteer
- Developed internal website using Vue.js
- Setting up scheduler (cron), caching (redis), Encryption for multiple purposes

#### **Undergraduate Thesis Internship**

Sep 2018 - Apr 2019

PT. Pertamina EP Asset-3 | Cirebon, Indonesia

- Seismic interpretation, Well-Seismic Tie, and result analysis
- Analyzing limestone reservoir distribution with Multi-Attributes Seismic

#### **Practical Thesis Internship**

Apr 2018 - May 2018

PT. Pertamina EP Asset-3 | Cirebon, Indonesia

Seismic interpretation, Well-Seismic Tie, and result analysis

## Educations

Hacktiv8 Full Stack Javascript Immersive Full Stack Javascript	Apr 2021 - Jul 2021
Institut Teknologi Sepuluh Nopember Bachelor's Degree   Geophysical Engineering (GPA 3.04/4.00)	Aug 2014 - Aug 2019

## Certifications

Sanbercode Python Advanced Data Science Training	Sep 2020
Sanbercode Python Data Science Training	Aug 2020
Occupational Health and Safety (Ahli K3 Umum) by The Ministry of Manpower of the Republic of Indonesia	Nov 2019
Paradigm SeisEarth Software Training by PT. Paradigm Geophysical Indonesia	Jun 2017

# **Projects**

#### **Sudoku App for Mobile**

https://github.com/farel14/sugoku/tree/03-final

Tools: • JavaScript • PostgreSQL • React Native • Bootstrap • Redux • React Navigation

#### **Movie and TV Series App**

https://github.com/farel14/entertainme/tree/06-deploy

Tools: • JavaScript • Redis • Tailwind • MongoDB • React • AWS • Apollo GraphQL

#### **Pelit Money Tracking App for Mobile**

https://github.com/farel14/pelit-client | https://github.com/farel14/pelit-server

Tools: • JavaScript • React Native • Tesseract OCR • Supertest • PostgreSQL • Redux

#### Travel App (Jalan-Jalan Ngab!)

https://github.com/farel14/jalan-jalan-ngab

Tools: • JavaScript • Socket.io • Bootstrap • Express.js • PostgreSQL • ¡Query • Sequelize

#### **Auction Web App**

\_

Tools: • Python • SQLite • Django • CSS • Javascript

#### Yu-Gi-Oh! Wiki and Deck Builder App

https://kodok-sarjana.web.app/

Tools: • JavaScript • Sequelize • Yugioh API • Vue.js • PostgreSQL • Vuex • Bootstrap

#### **Hearthstone New Expansion Hype Analysis**

-

Tools: • Python • Pandas • Word Cloud • Matplotlib • Twitter API • SciPy • Beautiful Soup

#### **Quiz Score Counter Bot for Discord**

https://github.com/farel14/discord-quizbot

Tools: • Discord.py • JSON • python-dotenv

#### Music Album holder and Earphone Bag (3D model)

-

Tools: • Autodesk Fusion 360 • Ultimaker Cura

## Research and Publication

Application of Multi-Attributes Seismic for Analyzing Limestone Reservoir Distribution (Case Study: Upper Cibulakan Formation, North-East Java Basin)

Sep 2019

## Skills

#### Web

- JavaScript TypeScript Python
- Nest JS Express React React Native Vue.js Django Python
- HTML CSS & Sass Puppeteer

#### **Machine Learning**

- Python SciPy Matplotlib Pandas
- Discord.pyDiscord.js

#### **Database & Tools**

- PostgreSQL SQLite MongoDB Sequelize
- · Redis · Git · GitHub

#### Geophysics

- SeisEarth
   GeoDepth
   Echos
   VISTA Seismic
- Res2DInv ZondRes2d MATLAB

#### Occupational Health and Safety

- ISO 9001 ISO 14001 ISO 45001 ISO 31000
- JSA & CSMS BFF & BFA Health Regulation SMK3

#### CAD

Autodesk Fusion 360 (3D Design)
 Ultimaker Cura (3D Print)